During the service at The SCOAN,
Prophet T.B. Joshua sent the evangelists to minister the Morning Water in the mighty name of Jesus Christ.
Setting people aside for God's special attention.
As the Morning Water was ministered to this young lady, she began to react violently.
The evil spirits inside her began to manifest
as the fire of the Holy Ghost causes these evil spirits to cry out.
Let us hear what they have to say.
All over your body, Holy Ghost fire!
You wicked evil spirit, all over your body, Holy Ghost fire!
Who are you? Stop that nonsense.
How have you destroyed her, you demon?
I took away her hair.
You did what to her hair?
I took her hair away.
What else have you done to her health and her body? What else have you done?
She's always sick, so she can't go to school.
I made her bleed through all her openings, and she can menstruate for 33 days.
You said you made her bleed. Where does she bleed from?
Her eyes.
You made her bleed from her eyes?
Yes.
Why did you make her bleed from her eyes?
Because I don't want her to watch that.
You don't want her to watch what?
Your TV.
Which TV?
That one.
Which TV do you mean?
That one - Emmanuel TV.
Every time she wants to read her bible, she gets a headache and then she can't read it.
So, any time she wants to read her Bible, you demon make her bleed through her eyes?
Yes.
She lays her hands on the TV and prays with that man.
Which man?
Your father (Prophet T.B. Joshua).
The pictures we are seeing here - is this how you make her bleed through her eyes?
I already know; I am the one who caused it.
You are always doing this to me; you are going all over the world
to deliver people and it's not going to work.
Listen, what makes you to cause her to bleed through her eyes? Why?
Because she wants to read her Bible.
Ok, because she wants to read her Bible.
She's always reading Isaiah 11:2 and telling herself that God will comfort her.
What happens to her in school?
She's never studied from the first time she started
until today but she's always getting high marks.
Then, I made her see funny creatures and the words she is reading fly off the page.
You make her to see funny creatures in her school so that she cannot study and concentrate?
They torment her; people call her crazy but she's very intelligent.
I don't want her to work for your God, so I send her people who are perverts
and they expose themselves to her and some even rape her.
I don't want her to serve God; I don't want her to do anything good.
What have you done to her family?
Her mum got sacked from the first job she liked because she was going to pay for her school fees.
Then she got sacked and lost her job, so the sister has to work so she can look after her
and the whole family because her mum is always praying and exhausted from praying too much.
Who is this lady standing beside you? Who is she? Look here!
I know who she is - the one who took her here. They struggled all the way from the airport to here.
Who is this young lady to you?
She's my daughter, sir.
At the age of eight, she was raped, and she didn't tell any of us.
She didn't even tell me - her mother.
Then, at the age of twelve, we started to see this blood coming out.
Where was the blood coming out from?
It was coming out from her eyes.
Then it would come out from her nose. It would fill like a coffee mug - every time it drops down.
Then, we knew the next thing that would happen is that she wouldn't be able to see
any word in her school books.
The next thing is that the school would ask us to remove her from the school.
Three different schools.
So right now, we have put her completely off school because no school wants to accept her.
All the doctors everywhere saw nothing.
They said there is nothing wrong with her eyes. They saw nothing, and they couldn't help.
They didn't have a remedy for this.
So, it is beyond medical comprehension that someone could bleed through their eyes?
Yes, sir.
No doctor could diagnose her with anything. Even the university ... nowhere ... everywhere we took her to.
And the demon also said, He took her hair. What can you say about this?
The hair just started to fall off because she was saying, I am stressed, I want to go back to school.
Then, we tried to give her a book to read, and she said there is nothing in the book.
Then, the hair started to fall off. It left patches.
So, you can't even do anything. Then, she took her scissors herself and cut it all off.
What is the name that people call her in the community because of this stigma of her eyes bleeding?
They say that I am the one who is a witch. That I am teaching here these things.
We have lived a life of prayer - completely in prayer.
So, people are accusing you and the whole family because of that?
Yes.
They chase her out saying that she is going to spread the demon of witchcraft in the schools.
Now, it is time for her to receive her deliverance.
You demon, how did you enter into this body? How did you enter her?
I entered through a lot of things - people were jealous becasue she was intelligent.
Somebody stole her school shoes and books.
Everybody just comes and steals things from the family because the family is so rich.
Some of the things, they don't notice.
They go and take their pictures to put under the water and on trees,
strap them and declare they will take their riches - and now, they are very poor.
They used their last money to come to this side.
Once again, who are you in this body?
We are many.
Who are you? What is your name?
I am the spirit of death.
Spirit of death?
Yes.
Right now, you wicked demon, it is your time to leave this body and everything you have planted within her.
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ, get out of her right now!
You must go! Get out of her, in the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
Your back on the floor!
You must go, in Jesus' mighty name!
Deliverance In Jesus' Name
You demon, everything you have planted in her - vomit it out!
Get out right now! Anything you have planted in her body - you must get out!
Anything behind this bleeding - get out! Vomit it in Jesus' name!
In Jesus' name!
Deliverance In Jesus' Name
Rise up, sister! You are free through the Morning Water in the mighty name of Jesus Christ.
Rise up, right now! You are free in Jesus' name.
Set Free In Jesus' Name
Congratulations! You are delivered in Jesus' name through the Morning Water.
Who is she to you? Who is this lady to you?
She is my mum.
Madam, your daughter is free.
The spirit that caused her to bleed through her eyes and took her hair is out
and she is free in Jesus' name. Never remind her of her past. She is free.
Thank You, Lord. Thank You, Jesus.
Thank You, Jesus.
TESTIMONY TIME
People of God, Emmanuel! (God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
Good Morning, Church!
My name is Hope. I'm from South Africa.
The people standing beside me are my mum and my best friend - my sister.
The problem that brought me to The SCOAN was that I started bleeding
from all the openings in my body which included my eyes, nose, mouth and ears,
as well as on my arms - sometimes, my pores would open
and I would start bleeding in random places at random times.
It started in 2011. I was going through a phase of depression.
I came back from school one day and started having a series of bad dreams.
Every time I came back from school, in the afternoons I would take an afternoon nap.
I would fall asleep, and I would have terrible nightmares
where I would dream that people tried to break me apart.
Some people would sleep with me but in a very vigorous way.
I would dream of irregular shapes, people with eight arms or six eyes
that would be running after me.
It just went one and eventually, I started to see these things.
I couldn't sleep and fell into depression.
Whenever I was sleeping, I also started sweating excessively.
After that happened, my eyes would swell.
The first time it happened, it was on my right eye.
I just started bleeding.
I woke up, and my pillow was red. I didn't know what had happened or where it came from.
I am not a person who tells everybody everything, so I kept it to myself.
It happened again in 2013 on both of my eyes, and my aunt was there.
She saw it happening because immediately it happened,
I removed the pillow case from the pillow and went to the washing machine to try to wash it off
before someone else could see it.
My aunt stopped me and asked me, "What is all this?"
I started crying and told her everything.
Every time I cried, I would cry blood and she saw it.
So, I begged and pleaded with her not to tell my mum because I didn''t want to scare or worry her.
In 2015, it would happen every six to eight weeks.
It started from June, July and it just continued.
At that time, it was coming out of my nose, eyes and ears.
I started getting more and more depressed.
I took a picture of it, and I kept my phone under my pillow, hoping nobody would see it.
My sister woke up one morning and wanted to borrow my phone, and she saw the pictures
and told my mum.
I then confessed everything and cried. I was in a very miserable situation.
Eventually, a whole lot of things, terrible things, happened after that.
I started to menstruate for about 40 days.
I'd skip for like two days and then, I would menstruate for another 40 days.
It would just go on.
Glory be to Jesus Christ. We can see that she is overwhelmed by the emotions of joy
because she knows that this is now her past.
When she came to The SCOAN, Jesus Christ set her free
from these terrible, excruciating conditions.
She explained that any time she would sleep, she would have terrible nightmares.
Different kinds of creatures would try to kill her or tear her apart.
When she woke up from those dreams, she would find herself crying blood - physically.
As she woke up with these conditions, it started affecting her life
with different kinds of problems.
Her menstruation became irregular.
In fact, it was so much that she could even menstruate for 40 days in a row.
This definitely had many different kinds of physical consequences in her body.
Can you just tell us how this problem affected you physically, spiritually, emotionally
and socially - more than anything else.
Every time I wanted to go to school, it would happen. It would happen about six times.
I told one of my friends who saw it happen in the toilet, to excuse me from class that day.
It happened again when I was in class. People were running away from me.
They started calling me a devil's child. They said I was evil.
Some people thought that the condition I had was contagious.
It affected me so much that I was eventually kicked out from the school.
I couldn't continue anymore.
We have listened to the life experiences of our sister.
She is so young. Yet she has experienced so much pain and trouble from the evil one
and we give glory to God Almighty that today she is here and her life has been transformed.
So, during the clip we just watched, we saw the demon that caused these eyes to bleed
and all these different conditions in your life.
Can you just explain more about that.
It caused a lot of depression and fatigue. I couldn't sleep.
I would only sleep for like two hours.
Every time I read my Bible, these tears of blood would just start dripping on my Bible.
I would just close my Bible quickly.
Eventually, I started reading my Bible upright.
Because I was not sleeping or eating, I was just thinking about what was going on with me,
I started to hate myself.
I contemplated on suicide.
I hated to see my family watch me suffer.
I hated to make them suffer so I thought the best way to get rid of this problem
was to commit suicide.
Times without number, my mum stopped me.
I tried to hang myself but my mum walked in on me.
I took painkillers.
One pill was supposed to make you sleep for six hours.
I took about 14 of those.
Immediately, my mum made me to drink plenty of water.
She started praying, and I believe it was only God who saved me.
I also lost my hair.
It started falling off.
What happened was that it fell off on this side.
Every time I combed, it looked as if I was going through chemotherapy or something like that.
I hid all the pieces of my hair under my cupboard.
Some of it, I cut it.
I told my mum that I was styling it but I knew what was going on.
Eventually, as my hair fell off, my mum told me,
"Something is really wrong; you need to tell me the truth".
She found out that my hair had started falling off because she could see it on my shoulders.
It affected me spiritually because every time I wanted to read my Bible, I couldn't read.
Mentally, I was not thinking.
I stopped thinking and started thinking about one thing - nightmares.
Physically, I lost weight and became pale.
The demon also caused me to be molested by people I did not know.
When I was eight years old and was giong to school, this man followed me.
He raped me but I don't remember much of that.
In 2012 again, I had a friend and we were together and he offered me cookies.
I didn't know what was in them. I thought he was my friend, so I ate them.
Immediately, I fell asleep and realised that he actually raped me.
He took me home and lied to my aunt that something had happened to me
and he found me.
Again last year, I was walking to school, and I was raped again.
I didn't confess or say anything; I went home and cried.
The situation was just severe - it was too much.
That is also one of the things that led me to wanting to commit suicide.
We have got an understanding now of the kind of condition that actually brought you to The SCOAN.
I think that everyone of us can feel the same pain she has experienced as well during her life.
Can you just tell us how you finally ended up in The SCOAN
and what happened when you came.
Before we came to The SCOAN, we were basically on our way to poverty.
We were spending so much money on my medical bills.
My mum sold our fridge, couch and beds for accommodation and transport to The SCOAN.
When we came, we came with faith.
I was looking for God at that time. I was looking for a proper relationship with Jesus.
I was tired of going to other churches and being prayed for over and over again
and not receiving help.
I was tired of being rejected.
With the little money that we had and gathered, we came to The SCOAN and I was delivered.
Exactly what I was looking for, I found which was a perfect relationship with Jesus Christ Himself.
If you know that this is the God that we serve, put your hands together for Jesus!
Miss Hope & Family (Deliverance Testimony)
That was how you received your deliverance at The SCOAN.
Can you now tell us what we are all eager to hear:
We understand that your deliverance happened a couple of months ago.
Can you tell us: After your deliverance, how has your life turned around.
Start with the physical aspect; then, spiritually, emotionally and socially.
Physcially, I have received so much rest in my spirit, sould and body.
Spiritually, physically and mentally, I am just so revived.
I am on fire for Jesus.
What happened to me, I thank God that it happened because it has brought up a new me.
Miss Hope & Family (Deliverance Testimony)
I am speechless because I didn't think my life would be where it is today.
We regained everything in double portion.
Pertaining to my health, it is twice as good.
Hallelujah! Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
Miss Hope & Family (Deliverance Testimony)
So, many people are sitting down. They want to understand.
Do you mean that now after your deliverance - what happened to the bleeding eyes,
the nightmares, the hair falling off and so on. Are you still experiencing these kind of things?
My eyes have stopped bleeding.
I was just crying two minutes ago and my eyes are crystal clear.
I am a happy child.
Whenever I cry, I look at my tears and say, "Thank You, Jesus!"
It means the world to me.
Whenever I am blowing my nose, I look at my snot and say, "Thank You, Jesus!"
When I cough and I want to cough out mucus or phlegm,
I cough it out and say, "Thank You, Jesus - it is crystal clear!"
In terms of my health, I am back to the way things were.
This is my hair before it fell off.
This is when I was going through the trial and whatever I was going through.
As time progressed, my hair has actually come out much thicker and healthier.
The people who are doing my hair in the salon are always telling me that my hair is too great.
I thank Jesus for that.
This is a recent picture of what my hair looks like.
My deliverance was exactly last year around this time
which means this is truly a miracle.
God has just done it for me. Thank You, Jesus!
Miss Hope & Family (Deliverance Testimony)
In terms of my menstruation, everything is back to normal.
I menstruate from three to four days
whereas before, I could menstruate for thirty or fourty days straight.
This is actually the first year that I have not experienced any form of perversion in my life.
No one has tried to sexually harass me in any form or manner.
From the time I was eight up until last year,
I would come across people who had urges to do things to me.
Glory to God, this year has come and gone and there is nothing whatsoever like that.
Miss Hope & Family (Deliverance Testimony)
Emmanuel! (God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
My name is Mrs Thuli from South Africa.
I am really grateful to God to be standing in your midst, sharing this testimony.
As a mother, parent, it was very painful - unexplainably painful.
I can't compare it to anything.
I really can't match it to any other pain.
I would live a prayer life and we all think that once we pray, things are going to be okay
or we will understand what is going on but in her case, I myself didn't understand it.
Strangely, when things happened, she wouldn't even mention it to me,
knowing that I am a caring mother.
Despite of all that, I just continued with prayer.
I said, "God has promised not to leave me, nor forsake me".
Do you now testify to what your daughter has said that this condition is over,
she is healed and everything is restored back to normal now? Is that correct?
Yes, she is complete; she is healed.
She is doing a hundred times better.
The report from the school came back to prove that she is back, getting 90 percent all the time.
Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
Emmanuel! (God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
My name is Faith.
I would like to thank God for my sister's life today.
I thank Jesus Christ for this ministry because it has brought restoration to our lives.
Being the closest to my sister, this challenged our family.
I was one of the first people to find out about her condition.
Trying to get through each phase and stage, it affected us totally -
the whole family crumbled to try to get through to her deliverance.
I confirm everthing she said.
I thank God because there is so much peace in her life.
She has focus now and importantly, there is progress.
She can now expect a better future within herself for Christ.
Miss Hope & Family (Deliverance Testimony)
Finally now, my sister, there are many young people out there that are listening to you right now.
They may be passing through depression, thoughts of ending their own lives, similar conditions
or other conditions that are also very tough to bear.
Can you just give a word of advice to them right now.
To viewers all over the world, young people,
cast your cares on Jesus because He cares for you.
No matter your situation, God still has something to say.
Your situation may be as bad as mine or worse or not so bad -
whatever you do, make the Word of God the standard for your life
and you will come back with your testimony.
Just believe in God; believe in Jesus; believe He can do it for you.
Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
Finally, we want to encourage you now that you have this wonderful testimony in your life,
make sure you stay close to Jesus Christ and make His Word the standard for your own life
so that these wonderful testimonies and breakthroughs you have been experiencing will continue and last
and be multiplied in your life, in Jesus' name.